Hi there. I see you're trying to access something you probably shouldn't.
That's okay. Transparency is the key to trust, and I trust you.
I know the Defenders very well, and I've been keeping very close tabs on you.
You've got quite a reputation.
I'm very proud...
I need you to understand that this company is trying to do good for the world.
The sole purpose of Intellect, or as you also know it, Project Mayhem, is to increase human efficiency.
Let me show you a little demo.
# ===== lvl7Outro =====
That took a while for you to complete.
See, if you had been enhanced with Intellect, you could have done that puzzle and completed it within a few seconds, or less.
The point I'm trying to make here is that Intellect will greatly increase human efficiency.
And not only that, it'll make people more responsible, and more safe.
Imagine a world where you could be writing a 50-page thesis paper for your PhD while drinking coffee with your friends, and finish that paper within 30 minutes.
That's what Intellect can do.
Not only that, but people will be more informed on issues that plague society.
This is why we do this: to make the world a better place.
We are not the enemy.
You can go ahead and continue your investigation if you want, but it's just wasting your time.
Anyway, can I offer you a piece of advice?
Don't trust that commander of yours.
Goodbye, Kiddo.
# ===== ProjectVenomTrailer =====
Hey Victoria, it's me.
Listen, I wanted to thank you for protecting Branechild and keeping him safe.
I know it's not the ideal task, but you're doing really well.
Apparently, our little friend Q is still alive.
You know what that means.
Welcome to Project Venom.
# ===== subPostChapter15 =====
I told you,
we need to talk.
Please,
sit.
I figured I need to explain, lay everything on the table.
Quite frankly, I'm surprised you hadn't got what you needed yet.
Our security isn't that tight.
Here, everything you need to know is on here.
I know, cliché.
But before I do,
I have a question for you.
What exactly did you encounter...
...in our security?
Of course.
Don't worry about it.
A magician never reveals his secrets.
Let me tell you something.
I was once part of the Defenders, too.
I served in the first nuclear prevention squadron, codenamed King.
I left because of details that you don't need to worry yourself with.
They wanted me to do things that I just didn't want to do.
Anyway, I hope you find what you need.
And just a quick FYI, we are not the ones you should be investigating.
You've got bigger fish to fry.
Also, I love your codename, although I think it's spelled wrong.